techrigy.com 2007-11-02

# Techrigy | Privacy Policy

Techrigy Privacy Policy

Effective: **December 1, 2006**

## Our Commitment To Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## The Information We Collect

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the _Techrigy.com_ and _BlogBackupOnline.com_ website. On some pages, you can order products, make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected on these pages include: 

Name  
Address  
Email address  
Phone number  
Credit/Debit Card Information

## The Way We Use Information

We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that order.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

You can register with our website if you would like to receive news, updates, support, or technical information on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will be used for this purpose only.

You may unsubscribe from Techrigy mailings by emailing unsubscribe@techrigy.com.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above.

## Our Commitment To Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

## Our Commitment To Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

## How To Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please call us at 585-687-6202 or send an email to privacy@techrigy.com.

## BBB OnLine Privacy Program

Your privacy is important to us. By participating in the Council of Better Business Bureau’s BBBOnLine Privacy Program we have made a commitment to meet the program’s strict requirements regarding how we treat your information and have it verified by BBBOnLine. Further information about this program is available at [**www.bbbonline.org**](http://www.bbbonline.org/privacy/dr.asp "http://www.bbbonline.org/privacy/dr.asp")

All BBB _OnLine_ Privacy Program participants are required to work with the program's dispute resolution process. The Privacy Program will only accept complaints regarding the misuse of personally identifiable information by a website operator. For more information about the Privacy Program dispute resolution process visit [**www.bbbonline.org/privacy/dr.asp**](http://www.bbbonline.org/privacy/dr.asp "http://www.bbbonline.org/privacy/dr.asp")
